SURMA: Right.
苏美：对​​。
I don't know that this works.
我不知道这行得通。
Why is it [INAUDIBLE] all Jake?
为什么[听不清]都是杰克？
What did you do?
你做了什么？
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
JAKE: So we did an episode where we were looking
杰克：所以我们做了一集
at future JavaScript stuff.
在将来的JavaScript中。
SURMA: We did.
苏玛：我们做到了。
People liked that.
人们喜欢那样。
JAKE: Yes.
杰克：是的。
So what I thought we'd do is look at new stuff that's
所以我认为我们要做的是看看
already landed--
已经降落了
SURMA: Oh, I thought you were going to say,
瑟玛：哦，我以为你会说，
let's look at old stuff.
让我们看看旧的东西。
I was like, well, that doesn't make--
我当时想，那没什么
JAKE: Well, I think new stuff that's already landed
杰克：恩，我认为已经有新东西了
is probably how you would define old stuff, really.
确实，这可能是您定义旧内容的方式。
I feel like I'm doing a bad job of introducing
我觉得我在介绍方面做得不好
what this actually is.
这到底是什么。
So I'm just going to show you.
因此，我将向您展示。
SURMA: Let's look at ES3.
SURMA：让我们看一下ES3。
JAKE: Well, yes.
杰克：是的。
SURMA: Oh.
瑟玛：哦。
I was trying to make a joke, but--
我当时想开个玩笑，但是-
JAKE: Don't ever do that again, mate.
杰克：永远不要再这样做了，队友。
Just tell me what is going on here.
告诉我这是怎么回事。
SURMA: This is like the throwback
瑟玛：这就像倒退
to object oriented programming in JavaScript before we
在使用JavaScript进行面向对象编程之前，
had classes, isn't it?
上过课，不是吗？
JAKE: Exactly.
杰克：是的。
Yeah.
是的
SURMA: Where you define a function,
SURMA：在定义函数的地方，
and suddenly you can add properties
突然间，您可以添加属性
on the prototype of that function.
在该功能的原型上。
It sounds really weird, but that's how you did it.
听起来真的很奇怪，但这就是您的做法。
JAKE: So what's happening?
杰克：那是怎么回事？
Talk to me.
跟我说话。
SURMA: So you define a function Car.
SURMA：因此，您定义了Car函数。
I'm not going to talk about what's
我不会谈论什么
inside the function for now.
现在在函数中。
But then you can add things in the prototype
但是然后您可以在原型中添加内容
of this function called Car.
该功能称为Car。
And I think that prototype is used
我认为使用了原型
when you use the function with the new keyword.
当您将函数与new关键字一起使用时。
So if I say new Car, then the things
所以如果我说新车，那么事情
in the prototype in that thing I can use also,
在原型中，我也可以使用
on the instance of Car.
以Car为例。
That was a really bad explanation.
那是一个非常糟糕的解释。
JAKE: It was.
杰克：是的。
Yes.
是。
SURMA: I always found it confusing.
瑟玛：我总是觉得很困惑。
It's-- what is it called-- in prototypical inheritance?
原型继承是什么？
JAKE: Yes.
杰克：是的。
SURMA: Something like that?
瑟玛：类似的东西吗？
JAKE: Prototypical.
杰克：典型的。
Prototypical.
典型的。
But what about--
但是关于 -
SURMA: You're just already doing weird stuff.
SURMA：您已经在做一些奇怪的事情。
JAKE: This.
杰克：这。
So I guess we should explain that you
所以我想我们应该解释你
were relatively recent to the web,
是相对较新的网络，
but you have ramped up fast.
但是您的速度很快。
SURMA: Yeah, I never did--
SURMA：是的，我从来没有
JAKE: You would have never have done this.
杰克：你永远都做不到。
SURMA: I've done it at university.
SURMA：我已经在大学里做到了。
Not that specific.
没有那么具体。
I just used [? Car.prototype ?] [? dot ?] first function equals
我刚刚用过[？ Car.prototype？] [？点？]第一个函数等于
and then the function.
然后是功能。
JAKE: But this Car inherits from Vehicle.
杰克：但是这辆车继承自车。
And this is how we used to do inheritance.
这就是我们过去进行继承的方式。
SURMA: But that's disgusting.
瑟玛：但这真令人恶心。
JAKE: Yes.
杰克：是的。
Isn't it?
是不是
Isn't it horrible?
是不是很恐怖？
SURMA: Wow.
瑟玛：哇。
JAKE: Because I mean--
杰克：因为我的意思是-
SURMA: That's why people use frameworks, right?
SURMA：这就是为什么人们使用框架，对吗？
Or little libraries that would give you that.
或很少图书馆会给你的。
JAKE: Exactly.
杰克：是的。
And so because you want Car.prototype
因此，因为您想要Car.prototype
to be an instance of Vehicle.
成为Vehicle的实例。
But Vehicle has-- you need to call the function with stuff.
但是Vehicle具有-您需要使用东西来调用该函数。
It has options and things.
它具有选项和事物。
So what you needed to do is create a new constructor,
因此，您需要做的是创建一个新的构造函数，
copy the prototype over, or reference the prototype over,
复制原型，或引用原型，
create a new one of those, and that meant your Car now
创建一个新的，这意味着你的车现在
inherits from Vehicle.
从Vehicle继承。
And then here, this is where you were doing the [INAUDIBLE]..
然后在这里，您正在执行[音频不清晰]。
My point is we've got classes.
我的意思是我们有课程。
This is what we have now.
这就是我们现在所拥有的。
So this is what I want to talk about,
这就是我想谈的
is just some of the things that we've got now--
只是我们现在所拥有的一些东西-
SURMA: And we're taking for granted almost, isn't it?
瑟玛：而且我们几乎理所当然地是不是？
JAKE: And we almost take for granted.
杰克：我们几乎认为是理所当然的。
SURMA: The old version, the prototypical inheritance,
SURMA：旧版本，原型继承，
always reminds me of Lua, where you only have tables
总是让我想起Lua，那里只有桌子
and you have tables within tables
并且您在表格中有表格
if you want to inherit-- it just gets super weird.
如果您想继承-那就太奇怪了。
It feels very similar.
感觉非常相似。
And this is just--
这只是-
ha, feels better.
哈，感觉好些了。
JAKE: Never done Lua.
杰克：从来没有做过罗阿。
I'll take your word for it.
你的话我记住了。
What's happening here?
这里发生了什么事？
SURMA: You are defining a function called spin.
SURMA：您正在定义一个称为spin的函数。
JAKE: Correct.
杰克：对。
SURMA: Let's take a closer look.
瑟玛：让我们仔细看看。
So the options-- oh, OK.
所以选项-哦，好的。
So this is basically sanitization
所以这基本上是消毒
of the options object.
选项对象。
JAKE: Yeah.
杰克：是的。
SURMA: Which, you know, even there
瑟玛：哪怕是那边
is also [INAUDIBLE],, where you just
也是[听不清]，
define a syntax, what the options object would look like.
定义语法，options对象将是什么样。
Because otherwise, you would have to write this,
因为否则，您将不得不编写此代码，
and this is just like-- it took me a while to actually
这就像-我花了一段时间
understand what you were doing.
了解你在做什么。
And now I didn't read every detail,
现在我没有阅读所有细节，
because I recognized the pattern, because I've
因为我意识到了模式，因为我已经
written that before.
之前写过。
JAKE: Yes.
杰克：是的。
SURMA: If you don't know the pattern,
瑟玛：如果您不知道模式，
this would be a lot of reading time spent until you know,
直到您知道，这将花费大量的阅读时间，
oh, you were just checking that certain properties are present,
哦，您只是在检查是否存在某些属性，
and if they're not, using a default value.
如果不是，则使用默认值。
JAKE: Yes.
杰克：是的。
And this got a lot easier with object.assign,
使用object.assign可以轻松得多，
which was essentially what the library--
本质上就是图书馆
we all had to be doing something like object.assign,
我们所有人都必须做诸如object.assign之类的事情，
and that's what we'd use here, but nowadays--
这就是我们在这里要使用的，但如今-
SURMA: Destructuring with the full values.
SURMA：以全部价值进行销毁。
JAKE: Yes.
杰克：是的。
So what we see here, we're destructuring.
所以我们在这里看到的，我们正在解构。
We're giving it the default values,
我们给它默认值，
and then a default value for the option object there,
然后是选项对象的默认值
so it's entirely optional.
因此它是完全可选的。
But I brought this example for a reason.
但是我举这个例子是有原因的。
SURMA: Because I don't like it.
SURMA：因为我不喜欢它。
JAKE: Because you don't like it, do you?
杰克：因为你不喜欢，对吗？
SURMA: So I do like the structuring and default base.
SURMA：所以我喜欢结构化和默认基础。
I've gotten around to it a little bit.
我已经解决了一点。
I don't like it in the actual function parameter definition.
我在实际的函数参数定义中不喜欢它。
I prefer this where you destructure
我更喜欢你破坏的地方
in a separate place, because, otherwise, it
在另一个地方，因为否则
gets a little bit nested, and it looks a bit crammed.
有点嵌套，看起来有点塞满。
And especially if you have TypeScript,
特别是如果您有TypeScript，
it gets even weirder, because then the types just
它甚至变得更奇怪，因为然后类型
go all over the place.
到处走。
So when I use TypeScript, I often
所以当我使用TypeScript时
have a type that's called function name with the word
的类型称为函数名，带有单词
options appended to the end where
选项附加到末尾
I define what structure the options object have.
我定义选项对象的结构。
And then I have the first line in my function
然后我在函数中有第一行
will then assign the default values.
然后将分配默认值。
JAKE: Yeah, and I agree.
杰克：是的，我同意。
Yeah.
是的
This looks a lot neater.
这看起来很整洁。
The reason I would still do this is because a static analyzer
我仍然会这样做的原因是因为静态分析仪
knows that these are the properties of the option
知道这些是选项的属性
object.
宾语。
In this case, it's not--
在这种情况下，不是-
SURMA: True.
苏尔玛：是的。
This is probably preferable if you don't have TypeScript.
如果没有TypeScript，则可能更可取。
JAKE: Right.
杰克：对。
So that's that.
就是这样。
SURMA: What's happening here?
瑟玛：这是怎么回事？
JAKE: If you don't know what's happening here--
杰克：如果您不知道这里发生了什么，
SURMA: I need to get out.
苏玛：我需要出去。
JAKE: We have to fire you, yeah.
杰克：我们必须解雇你，是的。
SURMA: You're making the DOM element with a class whatever
SURMA：您正在使用一个类来制作DOM元素
be 100 pixel tall.
100像素高。
JAKE: Well saved.
杰克：好保存。
So I spend a lot of my time designing in DevTools.
因此，我花了大量时间在DevTools中进行设计。
I'll throw some rough styles just into the editor,
我将一些粗略的样式添加到编辑器中，
and then I'll go into DevTools and that's
然后我将进入DevTools，
where I'll be shifting values around to make it look then--
然后，我将在其中转移值以使其具有外观-
SURMA: Copy and paste.
SURMA：复制并粘贴。
JAKE: It's exactly that, yeah.
杰克：就是这样。
In this case, editing this in DevTools
在这种情况下，请在DevTools中进行编辑
is hard, because what I want--
很难，因为我想要的是
in this case, I want whatever to be the same width
在这种情况下，我希望宽度相同
as it is high.
因为它很高。
I want it to be square is how a human would say that.
我要说的是正方形，这是人类会怎么说的。
And it means that if I'm shifting values around
这意味着如果我要转移价值
in DevTools, I shift one, and then I
在DevTools中，我先移一个，然后
have to Tab twice, or whatever, and shift the other one.
必须按两次制表键或其他选项，然后移动另一个。
And that's a pain.
那是一个痛苦。
So here's one of the solutions.
因此，这是解决方案之一。
SURMA: Yes, that's the proper solution, I'd say.
SURMA：是的，我会说这是正确的解决方案。
JAKE: Yeah, and it's been nice now that this is supported
杰克：是的，现在很高兴得到了支持
in all modern browsers.
在所有现代浏览器中。
I've just found this a dream, and it's--
我刚刚发现了这个梦想，这是-
SURMA: For what it's worth, size is coming to CSS.
SURMA：就其价值而言，CSS的大小已经到来。
JAKE: Is that right, and it's just
杰克：是的，那只是
an alias width plus height.
别名宽度加高度。
Oh, that's exciting.
哦，真令人兴奋。
SURMA: Yeah, because we have a lot of other things.
SURMA：是的，因为我们还有很多其他事情。
For example, I think background image size.
例如，我认为背景图片的大小。
Certain other size properties exist
存在某些其他尺寸属性
where you can have one value or two values,
您可以有一个值或两个值，
and if it's only one value, it's the same for width and height.
如果只是一个值，则宽度和高度相同。
But we don't have it for the actual size of the document.
但是我们没有文件的实际大小。
JAKE: So it becomes a shortcut for width and height--
杰克：所以这成为宽度和高度的捷径-
SURMA: Yeah, and you can also do size 100 pixel, 200 pixel,
SURMA：是的，您还可以制作100像素，200像素的尺寸，
if you want it to be 100 pixels wide and--
如果您希望它的宽度为100像素，并且-
JAKE: In the same way you do for background size.
杰克：以同样的方式处理背景大小。
SURMA: Exactly.
苏尔玛：是的。
JAKE: Oh, OK.
杰克：哦，好。
That's good.
那很好。
But in the meantime, this works.
但与此同时，这可行。
SURMA: For now, this works.
SURMA：目前，这可行。
JAKE: What's happening here?
杰克：这是怎么回事？
SURMA: I'm assuming that UL and LI are well-named variables,
SURMA：我假设UL和LI是名称明确的变量，
and you're not trying to throw me off.
而且你不是想让我失望。
So you have a list that you add a click handler
因此，您有一个添加点击处理程序的列表
and then you get the event targets from the LI,
然后从LI那里获得事件目标，
and if it's not an LI, then you say, well, you bubble up.
如果不是LI，那么您会说，好吧，您就冒了出来。
Oh, OK.
哦好的。
So what you're doing is you, basically,
所以基本上你就是在做你
do the event delegation where you have one click handler
在有一个单击处理程序的地方进行事件委托
on the UL of each individual list item,
在每个列表项的UL上，
and then you try to figure out, on the click event,
然后尝试在点击事件中找出
what is the actual list item that you click on.
您单击的实际列表项是什么。
JAKE: Yeah, so one event listener on the list,
杰克：是的，所以列表上有一个事件监听器，
but you're using it to detect a click on all the list items.
但您使用它来检测所有列表项上的点击。
That means you can move those list items around, add
这意味着您可以移动这些列表项，添加
and remove them.
并删除它们。
You don't have to change the list item.
您不必更改列表项。
SURMA: But then the problem becomes
瑟玛：但是问题就变成了
that if your list item has an anchor tag,
如果您的列表项具有锚标记，
that event or target might be the anchor tag within the list
该事件或目标可能是列表中的定位标记
item.
项目。
JAKE: It might just be the list itself.
杰克：这可能只是列表本身。
SURMA: Or it might
SURMA：或者可能是列表本身。
JAKE: Click to list item.
杰克：单击以列出项目。
SURMA: And then what you have to do
SURMA：然后您要做的是
is you have to walk up the tree manually
你必须手动走树吗
to find what the containing list element is, if it exists.
查找包含列表元素（如果存在）的内容。
JAKE: Yeah, and I always found this--
杰克：是的，我一直都这样
it's only a little bit of code, but it always
只是一点点的代码，但它总是
felt like a barrier to using event delegation.
感觉像是使用事件委托的障碍。
Whereas, now--
鉴于，现在-
SURMA: We've got closest.
瑟玛：我们最近。
JAKE: We've got closest, and it's so good, because it
杰克：我们离得最近，太好了，因为它
doesn't have to be a tag name.
不必是标签名称。
It could be a class name.
它可以是一个类名。
SURMA: I wonder if I did a "Supercharged" episode on this?
SURMA：我想知道我是否为此做过“增压”节目吗？
Oh, wait.
等一下。
I did.
是的
JAKE: Oh, right.
杰克：哦，对。
I did worry that maybe there's going
我确实担心也许会发生
to be a lot of crossover between what I show now
我现在展示的东西之间有很多交叉
and "Supercharged."
和“增压”。
SURMA: This is just because, as far as I know,
瑟玛：这是因为据我所知，
closest was inspired by jQuery, and at the jQuery series.
最接近的灵感来自jQuery，以及jQuery系列。
JAKE: There might be some of those coming up as well.
杰克：也许还会有一些。
Let's carry on.
继续吧
What is happening here?
这是怎么回事
Good luck.
祝好运。
SURMA: All right.
苏尔玛：好的。
Wait, wait.
等等。
So you're replacing just a plus?
因此，您要替换的只是一个加号？
Anything before the plus will that match pluses?
加号之前的所有内容都会匹配加号吗？
JAKE: Yes, that would be a literal plus.
杰克：是的，那是字面上的加法。
SURMA: Wow, that is confusing, because usually the plus means
SURMA：哇，这很令人困惑，因为通常加号表示
the preceding matcher once or many times repeated.
前面的匹配器重复一次或多次。
JAKE: But if there's no preceding matcher--
杰克：但是如果没有前面的匹配者，
I'm pretty sure that works.
我敢肯定那行得通。
Some of these I haven't checked thoroughly.
其中一些我还没有彻底检查过。
SURMA: I would probably backslash it for clarity
SURMA：为清楚起见，我可能会反斜杠
anyway, unless it then breaks, because right axis.
无论如何，除非它随后断裂，因为是右轴。
JAKE: Get over the first line.
杰克：越过第一行。
SURMA: We are replacing pluses with spaces.
瑟玛：我们正在用空格代替加号。
And then we have a result--
然后我们得到一个结果
oh, you are totally parsing your alts, aren't you?
哦，您正在完全解析自己的替代项，不是吗？
JAKE: Yes, I am.
杰克：是的，我是。
Well, specifically the query string.
好吧，特别是查询字符串。
SURMA: The query string.
SURMA：查询字符串。
Yeah, because spaces are in code.
是的，因为空格在代码中。
It's pluses and the individual parameters
优点和个别参数
are separated by ampersands, and then you
被与号分隔，然后您
do the [INAUDIBLE] split.
进行[音频不清晰]拆分。
Then, actually, in the end-- oh, you
然后，实际上，最后-哦，你
do the URI component decode.
进行URI组件解码。
That is a lot of work.
那是很多工作。
JAKE: It's a lot of work, and it looks--
杰克：这是很多工作，而且看起来-
SURMA: And it's frustrating, because the browser can
SURMA：这令人沮丧，因为浏览器可以
actually understand it in coding, and doing it
在编码中真正理解它，并做到这一点
yourself is super frustrating.
自己真让人沮丧。
JAKE: Exactly.
杰克：是的。
And it's useful to look at the URL to decide stuff.
查看URL来确定内容很有用。
It could either be the current URL,
它可以是当前URL，
or it could be the URL of a link,
或者它可以是链接的URL，
or it could be some form data that you're trying to send,
或者可能是您要发送的某些表单数据，
because it's the same in coding.
因为在编码上是一样的
And having to do this to figure it out--
而且必须这样做才能弄清楚-
SURMA: URL search parents.
SURMA：URL搜索父母。
JAKE: It's just so much nicer that we have that now,
杰克：我们现在有了它，真是太好了，
and we have that across all modern--
我们在所有现代领域都拥有这一点
SURMA: I'm still very annoyed that they
SURMA：我仍然很生气
didn't add a new property onto the location object.
没有在位置对象上添加新属性。
JAKE: So do you know why?
杰克：那你知道为什么吗？
So if you do new URL and parse a URL in,
因此，如果您执行新的URL并解析其中的URL，
you now have URL.search parameters,
您现在有了URL.search参数，
which is an instance of this, which you
这是一个实例，你
represent in the query string.
在查询字符串中表示。
The problem is the location object
问题是位置对象
is available across windows.
跨Windows提供。
SURMA: Oh, so if I open a window,
瑟玛：哦，所以，如果我打开一个窗户，
I can get access to the--
我可以访问-
JAKE: Yeah, and even if that window is in another process,
杰克：是的，即使那个窗口在另一个进程中，
like an iframe, you still have access to the location object,
像iframe一样，您仍然可以访问位置对象，
and this has been the whole problem
这就是整个问题
of implementing that, is having this extra object that exists.
实现这一点的原因是存在这个额外的对象。
SURMA: Why is that a problem?
SURMA：为什么会有问题？
JAKE: Because we have window proxy, and so we would need
杰克：因为我们有窗口代理，所以我们需要
the equivalent of a search parameter's proxy,
等同于搜索参数的代理，
because of things like [INAUDIBLE] and all
因为诸如[音频不清晰]之类的
of that sort of stuff, it's not referencing
这样的东西，它不是在引用
exactly the same object.
完全相同的对象。
SURMA: I would be fine if we just defined
SURMA：如果我们定义的话，我会好的
a [INAUDIBLE] function that just gives me a new instance.
一个[音频不清晰]函数，它只是给我一个新实例。
JAKE: In the same realm or something.
杰克：在同一个领域。
SURMA: Every time I do new URL search,
SURMA：每次我进行新的URL搜索时，
new URL and then location.string or something--
新网址，然后是location.string或其他内容-
it's a small [INAUDIBLE] compared
比起[听不清]
to what we had to do before.
到我们之前要做的
JAKE: Agreed.
杰克：同意。
It's work-aroundable, but it would be nice if it was there.
这是可以解决的，但如果在那儿会很好。
But yeah, this [INAUDIBLE] it does
但是，是的，它[听不清]
the encoding, the decoding.
编码，解码。
And it's just there, and it's brilliant.
它就在那里，而且很棒。
Excellent.
优秀的。
SURMA: Ah, FileReader.
SURMA：啊，FileReader。
I'm not sure about FileReader.
我不确定FileReader。
So it was supposed to help you read Blobs and files that
因此，它应该可以帮助您读取Blob和文件
are given from file picker and these kind of things.
是从文件选择器中获得的。
And it's this super non promise based
这是基于超级非承诺的
API, which are always great.
API，总是很棒的。
It's like [INAUDIBLE] but for files, in a way.
就像[听不清]，但是对于文件来说，是某种方式。
Is the support super flaky across
是支持超片状
browsers or is this actually--
浏览器，或者实际上是-
JAKE: No, this is well-supported.
杰克：不，这是有根据的。
As you say, it predates promises.
正如您所说，它早于承诺。
It will take a Blob or a file, because file
这将需要一个Blob或一个文件，因为file
inherits from Blob.
从Blob继承。
And if you wanted to take that--
如果您想接受-
because Blob, you don't get access to the bytes.
因为Blob，您无法访问这些字节。
If you want access to the bytes, as
如果要访问字节，则为
like text or an array buffer, this
如文本或数组缓冲区
is the mess you would have to deal with.
是您必须处理的一团糟。
Nowadays [INAUDIBLE].
如今[听不清]。
SURMA: [INAUDIBLE] that you recently tweaked it, I think,
SURMA：[听不清]您最近对其进行了调整，我认为，
and that's where I learned it.
这就是我学到的东西。
Yeah, I never thought about abusing response in that way.
是的，我从没想过以这种方式滥用回应。
I don't think it's actually abuse, because--
我认为这实际上不是滥用行为，因为-
JAKE: It's creating a response when you don't really
杰克：当你真的不真正的时候，它正在创造一个回应
need to just because it has these methods on there.
只需要因为它上面有这些方法。
SURMA: But it's suddenly promise based, [INAUDIBLE]
瑟玛：但这突然基于承诺，[听不清]
because actually, you know what's going on,
因为实际上，您知道发生了什么事，
and I think that's a big difference.
我认为那是一个很大的不同。
JAKE: And that's one of the things, when we designed
杰克：那是我们设计的一件事
the response API, we wanted it to be very easy to get
响应API，我们希望它很容易获得
these other formats out like text or array buffer,
这些其他格式，例如文本或数组缓冲区，
those sort of things.
这些东西。
Nice promise based API.
不错的基于诺言的API。
Obviously, async functions are a thing
显然，异步功能是一回事
we didn't used to have that I take for granted now.
我们以前不曾拥有我现在想当然的东西。
It all made browsers so much easier.
这一切都使浏览器变得更加容易。
So the last one.
所以最后一个。
SURMA: Wait, what?
瑟玛：等等，什么？
JAKE: If you could at least get a flavor
杰克：如果你至少能尝到一点味道
for what's going on here.
对于这里发生的事情。
SURMA: We are creating a styles object.
SURMA：我们正在创建一个样式对象。
We are creating a random animation.
我们正在创建一个随机动画。
Generating the animation [INAUDIBLE] wide translation
生成动画[音频不清晰]广泛翻译
and we add the new styles, then we add that new animation
然后添加新样式，然后添加新动画
to an object, wait for--
到一个对象，等待-
JAKE: Do you know what?
杰克：你知道吗？
I'll save you time.
我会为您节省时间。
This is if you're wanting to create
这是如果您要创建
a programmatic animation.
程序动画。
SURMA: I see.
苏玛：我明白了。
Because back in the day you only had CSS.
因为在过去，您只有CSS。
JAKE: Yes, so if I wanted to animate from something
杰克：是的，所以如果我想从某件事上做动画
to something else, this is the kind of thing I have to do.
对于其他事情，这是我必须要做的事情。
I have to create the key frames.
我必须创建关键帧。
SURMA: AD hoc the key frame animation,
SURMA：AD hoc关键帧动画，
add it as a styles tag.
将其添加为样式标签。
JAKE: And this is because an animation could end
杰克：这是因为动画可能会结束
or it could cancel, so I need to listen for both to know
否则它可能会取消，所以我需要聆听两者才能知道
when the animation is done.
动画完成后。
And turn that into a promise.
并将其变成诺言。
Ta-da.
-
SURMA: Web animation's API.
SURMA：Web动画的API。
It's finally coming to a point where it
终于到了一个地步
becomes usable across browsers.
跨浏览器变得可用。
JAKE: Yeah, and this is themed differently
杰克：是的，这是不同的主题
from the other examples because we still don't have this.
来自其他示例，因为我们仍然没有这个。
SURMA: We have it in Chrome, at least a subset.
SURMA：我们在Chrome中至少有一个子集。
JAKE: We don't have the finished promise.
杰克：我们还没有完成承诺。
SURMA: No, we don't.
瑟玛：不，我们没有。
We sold out.
我们卖光了。
That's true.
确实如此。
JAKE: And do you know whose fault that is?
杰克：你知道那是谁的错吗？
SURMA: My mom's?
瑟玛：我妈妈是？
JAKE: By extension, yes.
杰克：是的，是的。
It's my fault, because at the time that he designed this,
是我的错，因为在他设计这个的时候，
we hadn't decided what to do with cancellable promises
我们尚未决定如何处理可撤销的承诺
at the time.
当时。
And because finished is a promise that may cancel,
而且由于完成承诺可能会取消，
I put the brakes on, and said we can't ship this yet, because it
我踩了刹车，说我们还不能发货，因为它
might turn out to be--
可能是
SURMA: Ladies and gentlemen, please tweet at Jake.
SURMA：女士们，先生们，请在Jake发表推文。
JAKE: I'm sorry.
杰克：对不起。
And do you know what's worse?
而且你知道更糟吗？
The thing they were doing is what we ended up doing.
他们所做的就是我们最终要做的。
So if we shipped it, it would have been fine.
因此，如果我们发货了，那就没问题了。
I used to do a JavaScript library for the BBC,
我曾经为BBC做过JavaScript库，
and we were having to target things like Safari 1.3,
而且我们不得不针对Safari 1.3之类的东西，
and this is the sort of stuff.
这就是那种东西。
All this stuff I'm showing you, I
我向你展示的所有这些东西，我
would have killed for this stuff back then.
那时会为这个东西杀了。
And it is nice to see that--
很高兴看到-
we look at the future cool stuff that might land,
我们看了未来可能降落的有趣事物，
and it's like, oh, that looks interesting.
就像，哦，看起来很有趣。
And it's nice to stop and look at that things have got better.
很高兴停下来看看情况已经好转了。
SURMA: We've got nice things now.
SURMA：现在，我们有了美好的事物。
JAKE: Things have got better.
杰克：情况已经好了。
I tend to, on stage, I lock my arms in.
我倾向于在舞台上锁定我的手臂。
I walk around like a camp zombie.
我像僵尸营一样走来走去。
SURMA: Is that a sweat fear?
SURMA：那是出汗的恐惧吗？
JAKE: I think it might be that.
杰克：我想可能就是那样。
So I'm a talking--
所以我在说-
and here's how this is working.
这就是它的工作方式。
SURMA: T rex mode engaged.
SURMA：进入霸王模式。
JAKE: Typing on my keyboard.
杰克：在键盘上打字。
Driving my car.
开我的车。